# Homework11
## Synopsis 
The  program should contain 5​ ​functions​ that will be mentioned later. Every time the
program starts, the first thing is identify which action does the user want to do. Number​ ​1~5
refers​ ​to​ ​the​ ​5​ ​functions​, and 0​ ​will​ ​terminate​ ​the​ ​program​. Before 0 is entered, DON’T
TERMINATE​ ​THE​ ​PROGRAM​. It has to execute the instruction given, and return​ ​to​ ​the
state​ where the user enters the instruction.
Please implement the program using “linked​ ​list”.
1. The first function is adding the information of the train that just arrived at the station.
A new​ ​line​ ​will​ ​be​ ​added​ ​to​ ​the​ ​bottom​ ​of​ ​the​ ​timetable​ ​if​ ​a​ ​train​ ​has​ ​arrived.
2. The second function is removing​ ​the​ ​information​ ​of​ ​the​ ​train​ ​that​ ​just​ ​left​ ​by​ ​its
number
3. The third function is searching for a particular train by its number
4. The fourth function is inserting a new train into current timetable. Sometimes the
railway company needs to schedule more trains to handle an influx of huge crowd.
5. The fifth function is removing a train from current timetable. Some mechanical
problem might popped up just before the train arrive, so the schedule must be
cancelled. 
## Contributor
Ping-Mao, Huang 
